To enhance your user experience, support technical features, and personalize content and ads, this site uses cookies.

Your use of Kongregate’s Services is subject to our revised [Cookie Policy](https://www.kongregate.com/cookie-policy), [Privacy Policy](https://www.kongregate.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://www.kongregate.com/terms-of-service).

Games Achievements My Kong Sign In

Games Achievements My Kong Sign In

X Complete Initialization **for [10 kreds](https://www.kongregate.com/kreds)** Complete the Quest and earn **an exclusive shiny kongpanion + 10 kreds** 15%

« Previous

Next »

**Congratulations!** You’ve completed your Kongregate account!

Keep exploring Kongregate with more [badges](https://www.kongregate.com/badges) and [games](https://www.kongregate.com/top-rated-games?sort=newest)!

**Congratulations!** You’ve completed your Kartridge quest!

Spend your hard earned kreds on some of [these games](https://www.kongregate.com/community-favorite-games)!

Hide the progress bar forever? Yes No

Privacy Policy
==============

**WE HAVE UPDATED OUR PRIVACY POLICY.** To further protect your privacy, starting on or after July 1, 2022, if you have not logged in or used our services for a consecutive period of at least three (3) years, your personal information and account may be deleted automatically and without further notice. Please review our Privacy Policy below for more details.
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| PURPOSE: | We, at Kongregate Inc. (**“Kongregate,”** the **“Company,”** **“we”** or **“us”**), are committed to respecting your privacy and the integrity and security of your personal information. As the data controller of certain of your personal information, we want you to know how we handle it, how we use it, process it and/or share it, as well as the ways in which you can protect your own privacy.  <br>  <br>Our Privacy Policy explains:  <br><br>* what information we collect and how we use it;<br>* with whom we may share your information;<br>* how long we retain and how we protect the information; and<br>* what rights and options you have to control your personal data. |
| SCOPE: | This Privacy Policy applies to any and all end users of Kongregate’s services (**“Services”**). Your use of the Services are subject to this Privacy Policy, the [Cookie Policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/cookie-policy?external-link=true')) (which is incorporated into the Privacy Policy) and the [Terms of Service.](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/terms-of-service?external-link=true'))  <br>  <br>Each of [www.kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/?external-link=true')), [www.kartridge.com](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/?external-link=true')), and all other sites or online services that are owned or operated by Kongregate currently or in the future is a **“Site,”** and collectively, the **“Sites.”** Each mobile game published or operated by Kongregate currently or in the future is an **“App,”** and collectively, the **“Apps,”** (and together with the Sites, the **“Platform”**). Each Kongregate game that can be played through third party platforms, e.g., via consoles, PCs and/or social media sites such as Facebook is a **“Third Party Platform Games.”**  <br>  <br>**Amendments to Privacy Policy.** We reserve the right to change our practices and to amend this Privacy Policy at our discretion and at any time. When any changes are made, we will try to provide reasonable notice and will post the updated version on the Platform. We may also send an email, in-game message or provide notice within some or all of our Services when this Privacy Policy changes. Each time a user accesses our Services, the Platform or Third Party Platform Games, the then current version of the Privacy Policy applies, and you agree that the information we collect will be subject to the Privacy Policy, as updated. We encourage you to check this page regularly so that you know our current practices.  <br>  <br>**General Application Clause**  <br>  <br>The descriptions of how we process your personal data, your rights, and limitations to processing your personal data that are mentioned in this privacy policy apply to you when you use our services. They are based on the rules of the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), which applies when you reside in the European Union and use our Services.  <br>  <br>If you do not reside in the European Union and use our Services, the descriptions of this privacy policy may not fully apply to you and other data protection laws might be applicable. If you are a resident of the State of California, please see the Section below titled: Additional Information Regarding California Residents for detailed information according to the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”).  <br>  <br>We ask that you read the Privacy Policy carefully and familiarize yourself with its content. Should you have any questions about the changes, you are welcome to contact us at [support@kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL(mailto: support@kongregate.com). If you do not agree with the changes, then unfortunately, we must ask you to cease using our Platform and/or Services, as we must have all users under the same terms in order to provide equitable Services to all. |
| LAST UPDATED: | May 21, 2024 |
| LAST REVIEWED: | September 7, 2023 |

TABLE OF CONTENTS
-----------------

1. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE USE IT & OUR LEGAL BASES FOR PROCESSING IT
2. WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
3. DATA RETENTION
4. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
5. OUR POLICIES CONCERNING CHILDREN
6. YOUR RIGHTS AND OPTIONS
7. TRANSFER OUT OF EUROPE
8. DATA PROTECTION OFFICER
9. QUESTIONS, CONCERNS OR REQUESTS

1\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE USE IT & OUR LEGAL BASES FOR PROCESSING IT
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

When you access, connect to, sign up to, participate in, create an account for, make purchases within or otherwise use our Services, we may collect personal data from you. The personal data we collect will depend on the circumstances and the Services you are using. The personal data that we may collect about you and the purposes for which such personal data will be used, as well as the legal basis for such processing are explained in this section.

1. **Visiting our Site.** When visiting our Site, our system will automatically collect data and information from the computer system of the terminal device accessing the Site. In this connection the following data will be collected for a limited time period:
    
    1. visited website;
    2. quantity of data transmitted;
    3. information about the type and version of the browser used;
    4. the operating system of the user;
    5. the IP address of the user;
    6. the date and time of access; and
    7. the websites from which the system of the user arrived on our Site.
    
    Such data will be stored in log files of our system. Such data are needed only to analyze any malfunctions and will be deleted in approximately 30 days. The legal basis for temporarily storing data in log files is Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation (**“GDPR”**). Temporary storage of the IP address for the system is necessary for making the Site available to the terminal device of the user. For this purpose, the IP address of the user must be stored for the duration of the session. Data is stored in log files to ensure the functionality of our Site. In addition, such data is used to optimize the Site and to ensure the security of our IT systems. Data will not be analyzed for marketing purposes in this connection, and we will draw no inferences as to your identity. The aforementioned purposes also provide the basis of our legitimate interest in data processing within the meaning of Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR. Collecting data to make available the Site and storing data in log files is necessary for operating the Site. Consequently, users have no right to object to the collection or use of such data for the aforementioned purposes.
    
2. **Communication via Email and Phone.** If you communicate with us via email or telephone, we process all personal data you disclose to us during our conversation (e.g., you name, email address, telephone number, the reason why you are contacting us etc.). If you ask for help from our customer support team, we will collect and store the contact information you give them (generally, your name and email address) as well as information about your game play or activity on our Services, and your Kongregate username and/or social network ID number. Recipients of the processed personal data are our respective internal employees that are responsible for pursuing our purposes for the processing (e.g., someone from a department that you are contacting with a request).
    
    Depending on the specific conversation with you, the personal data can either be processed in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with us or to perform a contract you have concluded with us. In these cases, the legal basis for processing the personal data is Article 6(1)(b) of GDPR. Also, the processing can be necessary for us to comply with legal documentation obligations. Then, the legal basis for processing the data is Article 6(1)(c) of GDPR. The processing can also be necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interest to respond to mails and calls of yours when you contact us and are not our contractual partner as well as to have proof regarding substantial content of our conversation, including but not limited to cases of potential legal claims on our or your side. We may also store the communications you have with the Customer Support team in order to provide you support and improve the Services. The legal basis for processing the data in those cases is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR.
    
    The data is stored at least for the time until our contract with you is fully performed. If the data has been stored in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with us, we will store the data for as long as reasons objectively exist to believe that the respective conversation will be continued within the foreseeable future. Storage may also take place if this has been provided for by legal regulations such as directives, laws or other regulations to which the controller is subject. Data will also be blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the aforementioned standards expires.
    
3. **Account Information.** When you register for an account (**“Account”**), we process the following required data of yours: username, email address and whether or not you are a Child. Recipients of the processed personal data are our respective employees that are responsible for processing the data. We process the required data to enter into and perform a contract with you (Account contract) so you can use our Services. The legal basis for processing the data to enter into or perform a contract we concluded with you is Article 6(1)(b) of GDPR. Your Account data is stored for as long as you maintain your Account, which can be closed anytime at your request. To protect your privacy, your Account will be automatically closed and any such associated data automatically deleted after three (3) or four (4) years of inactivity, as further explained in Section 3.
    
4. **Information You Provide via Apps.** You may have the option to link your mobile account to your Sites account in connection with certain Apps. This will allow you to participate in content that crosses between the Sites and Apps, such as Kongregate level, points, and badges. If you choose this linking option, the information we receive via the Sites may also apply to Apps, and vice versa.
    
5. **Purchases.** When you place an order with us through our Platform we will request certain information from you, including, your name, email address, payment card details, billing address and phone number. We use a third party payment processor for this service. This information will be used to process your order, arrange delivery of your order and correspond with you in relation to your order. Recipients of the processed personal data are our respective employees that are responsible for fulfilling our Services. Our legal basis for using your personal data in this way is to perform the contract we enter into with you and to execute the customer service in respect of your order (Article 6(1)(b) of GDPR).
    
    The data is stored at least for the time until our contract with you is fully performed. If the data has been stored in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with us, we will store the data for as long as reasons objectively exist to believe that the respective conversation will be continued within the foreseeable future. Storage may also take place if this has been provided for by legal regulations such as directives, laws or other regulations to which the controller is subject. Data will also be blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the aforementioned standards expires.
    
6. **Online Presence in Social Media.** We maintain an online presence on social networks and platforms to communicate with clients, interested parties, and users who are active on those networks, and to be able to inform clients, interested parties, and users of our Services.
    
    Our Site therefore links to the website of Facebook, operated by Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA 94025, U.S.A., or, if you reside in the EU, Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Ireland, (**“Facebook”**). Otherwise, no data is exchanged with Facebook on our Site. For further information how Facebook processes personal data: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update')).
    
    Our Site also links to the website of Twitter, operated by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, U.S.A. or, if you reside in the EU, Twitter International Company, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, D02 AX07 Ireland. For further information how twitter processes personal data: [https://twitter.com/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://twitter.com/privacy')).
    
    When you access the aforementioned networks or platforms, the terms and conditions and data processing policies of the companies that operate those networks or platforms will apply. Unless otherwise provided in our data privacy policy, we will process data of users if they communicate with us through social networks or platforms, e.g., if they post on our Facebook pages, or send us messages.
    
7. **User-Generated Social Content.** As of January 2022, Kongregate no longer hosts forums or chat rooms. However, if you had posted in a forum prior to January 2022, then your previous posts are still publicly visible. If you had participated in a chat room prior to January 2022, all such chats have been deleted. Any member with an Account may still post game comments, (which are publicly visible), profile shouts and/or direct messages. When you do this, we process your username, date of your post and content of your post. The personal information that you post voluntarily through the Platform may be visible to others.
    
    We process the data to perform a contract with you so you can use our Service. Should you violate our terms of use (e.g., post offensive content) we will save such posts to prove the violation. We have a legitimate interest in making sure that the rules for participating in our forum are followed and toxic behavior of users can be properly sanctioned to ensure a friendly and respectful space for everyone. The legal basis for processing the data to enter into or perform a contract we concluded with you is Article 6(1)(a) of GDPR. The legal basis for processing data based on our legitimate interest is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR.
    
    The data is stored at least for the duration of the contract with you. If entitlements to claims arise from the contract we store the data for the respective limitation period according to the applicable law. Personal data that is processed based on our legitimate interest, will be stored as long as it is covered by such legitimate interest. The storage period in such cases is determined by the necessity of the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims (Article 17(3)(e) of GDPR), e.g., to have proof for a defense against unjustified claims within the respective statute of limitations by users who have verifiably violated our terms of use.
    
8. **Other Information You Provide.** We collect the following types of personally identifiable information: your contact information (such as name, postal or email address, or phone number), username and password, purchase history on our Platform, game play preferences (such as an interest in a particular type of game or genre), information you provide by interacting with us through social media, and photographs that you submit on our Platform or through our social media channels. By submitting a photograph, you waive any rights thereto and authorize us to copyright, use and publish the same in print or electronically for any lawful purpose.
    
9. **Information We Automatically Collect.** Kongregate, and our third-party partners in analytics, user acquisition, and advertising, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual or aggregated basis.
    
    * **Analytics.** When you visit our Platform, we automatically collect the following types of information: information about the devices you use to access the Internet (such as the IP address and the device, browser, and operating system type), URLs that refer you to our Platform and the dates and times of your visits, information on your gaming behavior on our Platform (e.g., page views, paths you take through our Sites, frequency of visits, referring/exit pages), general geographic location information (e.g., country) that shows where you are when browsing our Sites, search terms that you enter to reach our Sites or enter on our Sites to find products, and the fact that you opened one of our emails. We utilize analytics services to help us track the efficacy of our Platform and help us learn more about our users’ behavior.
        
    * **Information We Receive from Third Parties.** As previously noted, you can play Kongregate games through third party consoles or third party social media sites such as Facebook. When you play these Third Party Platform Games, backend system vendors may collect and share your information with us such as player IDs, session information, and purchase data, as well as personal information including email address, gender, and birthday and/or age range. Because such services are offered through a third party, this collection of information is governed by the applicable third party’s privacy policy.
        
    * **Tailored Advertising.** Advertising allows us to provide many free-to-play Services. Third-party advertising companies serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. Such advertising partners have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our Site in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement.
        
    * **Cookies.** As further described in our [Cookie Policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/cookie-policy?external-link=true')), we automatically collect information through cookies and other similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels, ad tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s). Cookies are small text files stored by your Web browser on your computer, phone, tablet, or other device used to browse our Platform. Cookies allow us to identify and authenticate visitors, track behavior, and enable important site features. We also contract with analytics services and third-party advertising companies to collect similar information for specific purposes. **_Please note that companies delivering advertisements on our Services may also use cookies or other technologies as described below in the section_ “Third Party Advertising and User Acquisition Partners” _and those practices are subject to those companies’ own policies._** You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. For more information on cookies, please see our [Cookie Policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/cookie-policy?external-link=true')).

2\. WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA.
------------------------------------------

1. **Service Providers.** We may use third party service providers to perform services for us such as to provide the infrastructure and IT services (including but not limited to data storage), process credit and debit card transactions, to provide customer services, collect debt analysis and improve data and process customer inquiries and perform other statistical analyzes. In the performance of these services, the third party vendors may have access to your personal data but are only authorized to process it strictly on our behalf and in accordance with our instructions.
    
2. **Third Party Advertising and User Acquisition Partners.** We have advertising on our Services so we can continue to offer many of our Services for free. Subject to your settings, we provide certain information to advertisers who will use them to serve you with ads in our Platform, and we measure who sees and clicks on their ads. We may also use aggregate information to monitor usage of our Services in order to help us improve and develop our Services, and we may provide such aggregate information to third parties, e.g., content partners or advertisers. This aggregate information does not include personal data and cannot be linked to you. When advertisers, ad networks or user acquisition partners place ads in our Services, they may collect or we may share the following types of information from within our Services:
    
    * performance data (like the number of clicks on an advertisement);
    * aggregated and/or de-identified information about you and other players collectively that is not intended to specifically identify you (like players between the ages of 21 and 25 who live San Francisco);
    * certain technical information (for example, IP addresses, non-persistent device identifiers such as IDFAs, and de-identified persistent device identifiers such as a hashed Android ID);
    * your social network ID;
    * and other contextual data about your game play (for example, your level and session length).
    
    The information collected may be used to:
    
    * measure how effective ads are, to offer you targeted advertising in order to personalize your experience by showing you advertisements for products and services that are more likely to appeal to you (a practice known as behavioral advertising), and/or
    * undertake web analytics (e.g., Google Analytics which is used to analyze traffic and other player activity to improve your experience).
    
    Advertisers or ad networks may collect this information through the use of tracking technologies like browser cookies and web beacons. After clicking on a third party advertisement, you may no longer be on our Platform. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the list of third party advertising and user acquisition partners and their privacy policies before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.
    
3. **Offer Walls.** Our Services may display an “offer wall” that is hosted by an offer wall provider. The offer wall allows third-party advertisers to provide virtual currency to players in exchange for interacting with an advertisement or for completing a marketing offer that may include signing up for an account with one of those advertisers. After clicking on one of these offers, you will no longer be on a site hosted by Kongregate or the social network through which you are playing Kongregate games. To properly credit player accounts and to prevent fraud, a unique identifier, in some cases your Kongregate username/ID, will be shared with the offer wall provider.
    
4. **Third Party Developers.** Most of the games on our Platforms are created by third party developers. These third party developers may request, by using Kongregate’s SDK and APIs, certain publicly visible information about users that play their games, e.g., your username, your user\_id (a numeric ID associated with your account that persists even if a username is changed) In order to fix bugs. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(b) of GDPR.
    
5. **Third Parties for Security or Other Legitimate Reasons.** We may also disclose your personal data to third parties, if we reasonably believe that disclosure of such personal data is necessary:
    
    * to comply with valid legal obligations including subpoenas, court orders, governmental requests or search warrants, and as otherwise authorized by law. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(c) of GDPR.
    * to protect our rights, property, or the safety of our customers, employees or the general public.. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR.
    * to protect against fraudulent, malicious, abusive, unauthorized or unlawful use of our Services and to protect our network, services, devices and users from such use. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR. We have an interest in providing our Services without fraud. This interest outweighs the user’s interest in not having personal data processed.
    * to advance or defend against complaints or legal claims. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR. We have an interest in defending against complaints or legal claims. This interest outweighs the user’s interest in not having personal data processed.
    * to determine credit risk. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR. We have an interest to assess credit risks in order to protect our economic interest. This interest outweighs the user’s interest in not having personal data processed.
    * or to obtain payment for our Services. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(b) of GDPR.
    * to outside auditors and regulators in case of legal obligations. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(c) of GDPR.
6. **Intra-Group Transfers.** We are part of a group of gaming studios that are owned by our parent company Modern Times Group MTG AB (“MTG”), a Swedish gaming company. This section explains how personal data may be processed with MTG and the reasons behind it:
    
    1. What Personal Data is Processed:
        1. MTG supports us in ensuring compliance with data protection laws. As part of this partnership, we may jointly process personal data such as names, email addresses, usernames, unique identifiers (e.g., game-ID players), and other necessary information to address your data protection requests effectively and in a timely manner.
    2. Purpose:
        1. Our objective is to provide you with a high level of data protection when you engage with our games. To achieve this, we receive support from MTG to ensure compliance with relevant data protection laws. This collaboration serves as a legitimate interest for both Kongregate and MTG, as well as our other group of gaming studios, and benefits you as our valued user.
    3. Recipients of Personal Data:
        1. The processed personal data may be shared with our providers of office tools and with MTG. These recipients are bound by contractual obligations and are required to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal data.
    4. Legal Basis:
        1. The legal basis for processing your personal data in collaboration with MTG is Art. 6 para. 1 let. c) and f) of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
    5. Data Retention:
        1. To demonstrate our compliance with data protection laws, we retain data protection requests for a specific duration. Due to this, data protection requests of yours will be stored no longer than necessary.
7. **Corporate Transaction, Reorganization or Bankruptcy.** In the event of a change of control, sale of some or all of our business or assets, corporate reorganization or bankruptcy, we would share the pertinent customer information (which may include your personal information) with the other business entity (or entities) involved in the transaction. In such an event, we would notify you via email and/or a prominent notice on our Platform of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(f) of GDPR.
    
8. **Legal Compliance.** We may disclose information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. The legal basis of this processing is Article 6(1)(c) of GDPR.

3\. DATA RETENTION
------------------

In the following you can find information on how long we store personal data in our systems which we have collected from you during your use of our Services. We adhere to a data retention policy that involves the retention of personal data from active users while concurrently deleting the data of inactive users who satisfy the subsequent criteria:

* Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years.

Furthermore, in compliance with legal authorities, we will keep a record of financial transactions in an anonymized form for the period of time required by law.

4\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
-----------------------------------

We strive to maintain the security of your personal information through a variety of security measures. Safeguarding your personal data is a priority for us. Personal data that you provide to us is stored on secure servers, and we use rigorous procedures to protect against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal data. Although we work hard to protect your personal data, please note that no system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to employ reasonable protections for your information that are appropriate to its sensitivity, we cannot guarantee that our safeguards will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use or disclose personal data, and we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of the information you share with us and we cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, loss or inadvertent disclosure of your information.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to any login or password information, and to your computer or device. To minimize the risk of having your account being compromised, we recommend that you set up your account password using unique numbers, letters and special characters. Do not disclose passwords to others. Please notify us of any password compromises and change passwords periodically to maintain account protection. To learn more about how to protect yourself online, we encourage you to visit the government’s website at [www.onguardonline.gov](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.onguardonline.gov')).

5\. OUR POLICIES CONCERNING CHILDREN.
-------------------------------------

**Our Services are Not Designed for Children.** Our Services, Platform and Third Party Platform Games are generally designed for and directed at people 18 years of age or older. No one under the age of 13 within the United States (or up to the age of 16 for children located in certain European countries)(collectively, **“Children”**) may provide any personal information to us, and we do not knowingly collect information from Children except in connection with the following Apps which Kongregate has designated as directed to Children (collectively, our **“Children-Appealing Games”**).

For our limited collection of Children-Appealing Games, we recognize a special obligation to further protect personal information collected from Children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without permission. Some of the features of our Children-Appealing Games are age-gated so that they are not available for use by Children. When we intend to collect personal information from Children, we take additional steps to protect children’s privacy, including:

* In accordance with applicable law, and our practices, obtaining consent from parents for the collection of personal information from their children, or for sending information about our Services directed to Children;
* Limiting our collection of personal information from Children to no more than is reasonably necessary to participate in an online activity; and
* Giving parents access or the ability to request access to personal information we have collected from their Children and the ability to request that the personal information be changed or deleted.

For additional information about our practices regarding Children’s personal information, please read our [**Children’s Privacy Policy.**](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/pages/childrens-privacy?external-link=true'))

With the exception of a handful or so of our Children-Appealing Games, Children should not attempt to create an account or send any of your information to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. If Kongregate learns that we have collected personal information from Children without verification of parental consent in contravention of these measures, we will terminate access to the account immediately and will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or other as required or allowed by law). If you believe that we might have any information from or about Children, please contact us at [support@kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL('mailto: support@kongregate.com')).

**Right to Remove Posted Information — California Minors.** If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account on the Platform, or through the Third Party Platform Games, you have the right to request removal of unwanted information that you publicly post on the Platform, or through the Third Party Platform Games. To request removal of such information, you can contact Kongregate using the email address associated with your account at [support@kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL('mailto: support@kongregate.com')) stating that you reside in California. Upon receiving such a request, Kongregate will make sure that the information is not publicly available on our Platform, or through our Third Party Platform Games.

6\. YOUR RIGHTS AND OPTIONS.
----------------------------

We understand that you may at times need further information from us regarding your personal data and how it is processed or that you may wish to update or correct the personal data you have provided us with. Your rights under GDPR include the following:

1. **Right to access your personal data.** You have the right to obtain confirmation from us as to whether or not personal data concerning you are being processed, and, where that is the case, access to the personal data and information.
2. **Right to rectification of personal data.** If you find that personal data that we process about you is inaccurate, you have the right to have us correct such personal data.
3. **Right to restriction of processing.** Under certain circumstances, such as if you question the accuracy of your personal data or you have objected to our legitimate purpose to process your personal data, you have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data until a solution has been found.
4. **Right to erasure of personal data (“right to be forgotten”).** Under certain circumstances, such as if your personal data has been unlawfully processed or you have withdrawn your consent (if the processing of your personal data is based on consent), you have the right to request and obtain erasure of your personal data from us, subject to certain exceptions. Please also note that any requests for removal do not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information from the Services. For example, content that you have posted may be republished or reposted by another user or third party.
5. **Notification regarding rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing.** We shall communicate any rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing carried to each recipient to whom the personal data have been disclosed, unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort. We will inform you about those recipients if you request it.
6. **Right to data portability.** If your personal data is processed by automated means based on your consent or for the fulfillment of our contractual relationship, you have the right to request that we provide you with your personal data in a machine-readable format for transmission to another data controller.
7. **Right to object to processing.** Under certain circumstances, such as if you question our legitimate interest to process your personal data, you have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, to such processing.
8. **Right to revoke the declaration of consent.** You have the right to revoke your data protection declaration of consent at any time. Revocation of your consent does not affect the legality of the processing that has taken place on the basis of your consent until revocation.
9. **We do not use automated decision making processes.** While you would have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing which produces legal effects that similarly significantly affects you, this would not apply for our Platform as we do not use automated individual decision-making.
10. **Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.** You have the right to lodge a complaint regarding our processing of your personal data with the supervisory authority of your place of residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement.
11. **Non-Discrimination.** At the risk of stating the obvious, we want to be clear that we will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights or other privacy rights. Unless permitted by **CCPA**, we will not take any discriminatory actions, including, denying you goods or services, charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties; providing you a different level or quality of goods or services; or suggesting that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

Please submit a request using this [**form**](javascript:util.openURL('https://kongregate-privacy.my.onetrust.com/webform/7424cb27-7013-49a6-a5a7-66b4bfa6c20e/167536ab-aa15-479c-8e0f-0b2911ce1d1e')) in respect of your rights. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to respond to your request within 30 days of receiving such request. If we cannot honor your request within the 30-day period, we will let you know the reasons why and when we expect to be able to fulfill your request.

If our processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw such consent at any time (this will however not affect the processing based on your consent before its withdrawal) by using this [**form**](javascript:util.openURL('https://kongregate-privacy.my.onetrust.com/webform/7424cb27-7013-49a6-a5a7-66b4bfa6c20e/167536ab-aa15-479c-8e0f-0b2911ce1d1e')) or by updating the settings in our Services (where applicable).

* **Updating Your Profile.** If you wish to review, edit or delete information you have provided to Kongregate, you may access your account information on the Site at any time by clicking on your username at the top of the Site homepage. We retain and use your information as necessary as described in **“Data Retention.”**
* **Opting Out of Promotional Emails from Kongregate.** If you are receiving Kongregate promotional emails due to prior consent and no longer wish to receive those email messages, you may opt out at the time you receive the message by following the instructions in that email, clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails or contacting us at [support@kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL('mailto: support@kongregate.com')). You will continue to receive non-marketing-related emails (e.g., material changes to the privacy policy, issues with the Platform or compromised data access).
* **Opting Out of App Notifications.** Kongregate Apps may send push notifications to your mobile device to provide game information, news, updates, or other relevant information. You can manage these updates from the “settings” page from within the App or from your device control panel that manages these notifications.
* **Opting Out of Social Media Platform.** If you wish to edit or manage the information Kongregate receives from a social media platform, you need to follow the applicable instructions at the specific social media site. For example, Facebook’s relevant policy in this regard can be found [here](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy/?entry_point=data_policy_redirect&entry=0')). Please note that once Kongregate receives any personal information from a social media site as a result of a user playing Third Party Platform Games, it will be stored and handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
    
* **Opting Out of Geolocation.** In order to improve and optimize our Service continuously, we use mobile tracking technologies. With the help of these services, we collect data on the usage of our Apps to be able to constantly improve our Services. In this respect, we may collect: IP address, which is anonymized right away, MAC address, anonymized Device ID (IDentifier For Advertisers (IDFA)) or Google Advertiser ID (GAID), browser type, language settings, internet service provider, network status, time zone, URL of the entry and exit pages, date of access and time spent, clickstream data, and other statistical information about the use of our Services. If you have previously allowed us to access your geolocation data, you can stop making geolocation available to us by visiting your mobile device’s settings for the relevant application or the “settings” page for the relevant App.
    
    The collection and storing of the data can at any time be disabled with effect for the future as follows:
    
    * In the case of an Apple device: Open the settings of your mobile device (e.g. iPhone or iPad) and select the menu item “Privacy.” Under “Advertising,” you can turn off the Ad Tracking.
    * In the case of Android devices: Open the settings in your App list and tap on the “Ad” button. When the Ad window has opened, you can deactivate the Google Advertising ID.
* **Opting Out of Third Party Tailored Advertising.** If you are interested in more information about tailored advertising and your choices to prevent third parties from delivering tailored web and mobile web advertising you may visit the following websites:
    
    * [Network Advertising Initiative Consumer Opt-Out Page](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/')) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Page for U.S.-based advertising](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.aboutads.info/choices/')); and
    * [Your Online Choices UK website for EU-based advertising.](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices'))
    * In addition, if you do not want to receive tailored in-application advertisements from third parties that relate to your interests in apps on your mobile device, you may opt-out by adjusting the ad tracking settings on your device. You can also reset the “Advertising Identifier” (like an IDFA) from your mobile device’s “settings” page, which will prevent continued use of existing behavioral data tied to the previous “Advertising Identifier.”
    * Further, depending on the platform provider (such as Apple or Google), you may be able to download apps, such as the Digital Advertising Alliance’s “AppChoices” app, that offer to provide you with control regarding the collection and use of cross-app data for tailored advertising.
    
    Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. While you do have choices to limit personalized ads that are tailored to your interests, you may receive generic ads. These opt-out tools are not provided by Kongregate but provided by third parties.
    
* **Opting Out of Analytics.** We use internal and third party analytics tools, including Google Analytics. The third party analytics companies we work with may collect and store data related to our Site, enabling the creation of user profiles under pseudonyms. These user profiles serve to analyze visitor behavior and are evaluated in order to improve and design our offer so as to meet the demands. Their collection and use of information is subject to their own privacy policies. You may opt-out of Google Analytics by following this [link](javascript:util.openURL('https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout')).
* **Controlling Cookies.** In order to design our Services in the most user-friendly manner for you, we, as well as many other companies, also use persistent and session cookies and web beacons and other similar technologies. You can manage many companies’ cookies used for online advertising via the consumer choice tools created under self-regulation programs in many countries, such as the U.S.-based [aboutads.info choices](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.aboutads.info/choices/')) page, Canada-based [www.youradchoices.ca](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.youradchoices.ca/')) or the EU-based [Your Online Choices](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/')). If you do not want cookies to be stored on your computer or wish to be informed of their storage, you can prevent the installation of cookies by declining to accept cookies or [managing cookies in your web browser](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/managing/')). However, we would like to point out that by preventing cookies, you may find that you cannot use all of our Platform’s functions to the full extent. For more information on our [Cookie Policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.kongregate.com/pages/cookie-policy?external-link=true')), please read here.
* **Contests, Sweepstakes and Promotions.** From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests, sweepstakes, surveys and/or other promotions on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you as provided in the terms of the corresponding promotion. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; in those cases, that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose.
* **Do Not Track.** Do Not Track is a concept that has been promoted by regulatory agencies such as the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC), for the Internet industry to develop and implement a mechanism for allowing Internet users to control the tracking of their online activities across websites by using browser settings. At this time, there is no general agreement on how companies such as ours should interpret Do Not Track signals. Kongregate does not currently respond to Do Not Track signals, whether that signal is received on a computer or on a mobile device. You can learn more about Do Not Track [here](javascript:util.openURL('http://allaboutdnt.com/')).

7\. TRANSFER OUT OF EUROPE
--------------------------

_IMPORTANT INFORMATION FOR EUROPEAN USERS: When you use our Services, your data may be sent to the United States and possibly other countries._

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area (**“EEA”**) and Switzerland, including at destinations that are not subject to a decision by the European Commission establishing an adequate level of protection of personal data. Currently, our servers are in the United States. Your personal data can be shared with other companies owned by our parent company, processed by staff working for us or for one of our suppliers, or shared with certain third parties who may be located outside the EEA and Switzerland. We will take all reasonable necessary steps, including entering into data processing agreements using standard contractual clauses, to ensure that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and have adopted appropriate safeguards to protect it.

8\. DATA PROTECTION OFFICER.
----------------------------

Kongregate is the “controller” in line with GDPR and other applicable data protection laws. Our external data protection officer is:

Prof. Dr. Christian Rauda  
GRAEF Rechtanswälte Digital PartG mbB  
Jungfrauenthal 8  
20140 Hamburg, Germany  
Email:[office@graef.eu](javascript:util.openURL('mailto: office@graef.eu'))  
Website: [www.graef.eu](javascript:util.openURL('http://www.graef.eu/'))

9\. QUESTIONS, CONCERNS OR REQUESTS.
------------------------------------

For questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy or the use of personal information you submit to us, please contact us at:

Kongregate Inc.  
10680 Treena Street, Suite 155  
San Diego, CA 92131  
Email: [support@kongregate.com](javascript:util.openURL('mailto: support@kongregate.com'))  

To exercise any of your privacy rights, please visit our Data Subject Rights Request Form available [here](javascript:util.openURL('https://kongregate-privacy.my.onetrust.com/webform/7424cb27-7013-49a6-a5a7-66b4bfa6c20e/167536ab-aa15-479c-8e0f-0b2911ce1d1e')). Through this form, you can specify the nature of your request and provide any information necessary to help us process your request efficiently.

Please note that we may need to verify your identity before processing your request to ensure the security of your data. The processing time for requests may vary depending on the complexity and nature of the request but we aim to respond within one month of receiving a verified request.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND USER ACQUISITION PARTNERS
-----------------------------------------------------

We use the following user acquisition and advertising partners, that are integrated into our Platform. Please check the following privacy policies to learn more about their privacy practices, including how you may exercise your data subject rights.

This list was last updated on July 12, 2023.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| AdAction | [https://www.adaction.com/privacy-policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.adaction.com/privacy-policy')) |
| AdColony | [https://www.adcolony.com/privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.adcolony.com/privacy-policy/')) |
| Adjust | [https://www.adjust.com/terms/privacy-policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.adjust.com/terms/privacy-policy')) |
| AdMob | [https://policies.google.com/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://policies.google.com/privacy')) |
| Adwords | [https://policies.google.com/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://policies.google.com/privacy')) |
| Appier | [https://www.appier.com/retargeting-privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.appier.com/retargeting-privacy-policy/')) |
| Apple Search | [https://searchads.apple.com/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://searchads.apple.com/privacy')) |
| AppLovin | [https://www.applovin.com/privacy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.applovin.com/privacy/')) |
| Chartboost | [https://answers.chartboost.com/en-us/articles/200780269](javascript:util.openURL('https://answers.chartboost.com/en-us/articles/200780269')) |
| Facebook | [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy')) |
| Fyber | [https://www.fyber.com/privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.fyber.com/privacy-policy/')) |
| HyprMx | [https://www.hyprmx.com/pp](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.hyprmx.com/pp')) |
| InMobi | [https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy')) |
| ironSource | [https://developers.is.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://developers.is.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/')) |
| Kidoz | [https://kidoz.net/privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://kidoz.net/privacy-policy/')) |
| Liftoff | [https://liftoff.io/privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://liftoff.io/privacy-policy/')) |
| Mintegral | [https://www.mintegral.com/en/privacy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.mintegral.com/en/privacy/')) |
| Moloco | [http://privacy.molocoads.com/](javascript:util.openURL('http://privacy.molocoads.com/')) |
| Pangle | [https://www.pangleglobal.com/privacy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.pangleglobal.com/privacy')) |
| Persona.ly | [https://persona.ly/en/privacy\_policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://persona.ly/en/privacy_policy')) |
| Super Awesome Ads | [https://www.superawesome.com/privacy-hub/privacy-policy/](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.superawesome.com/privacy-hub/privacy-policy/')) |
| TapJoy | [https://www.tapjoy.com/legal/#privacy-policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.tapjoy.com/legal/#privacy-policy')) |
| Tiktok | [https://www.tiktok.com/legal/privacy-policy-us?lang=en](javascript:util.openURL('https://www.tiktok.com/legal/privacy-policy-us?lang=en')) |
| Unity Ads | [https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy](javascript:util.openURL('https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy')) |
| Vungle | [http://vungle.com/privacy/](javascript:util.openURL('http://vungle.com/privacy/')) |

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION REGARDING CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
-----------------------------------------------------

1. **International Data Transfers.**
    
    If you are an EU resident, we rely on certain safeguards when sharing your personal data with a recipient established outside of the EEA/EU.
    
    Some vendors with which we share your personal data are established outside of the European Union. Principally, there are two possible safeguards we can rely on when we share your personal data with these recipients:
    
    * If a recipient is located in a country for which the European Commission has found it provides an adequate level of data protection, we rely on such a decision by the EU Commission. For recipients established in the USA we rely on the Transatlantic Data Transfer Framework, if the recipient is certified under this framework.
    * If a recipient is not located in a country with an adequate level of data protection according to the European Commission, we either have concluded a contract with this recipient in which we agree on rules to make sure the recipient takes adequate care of your personal data (EU Standard Contractual Clauses developed by the European Commission) or we rely on binding corporate rules of a group of undertakings or enterprises that have been approved by a supervisory authority.
2. **Information We Collect.**  
    Collection and Disclosure of Personal Information
    
    The chart below details which categories of Personal Information about California residents we plan to collect, as well as which categories of Personal Information we have collected and disclosed for our operational business purposes in the preceding 12 months. We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:
    
    * Directly from users of Kongregate’s services. For example, from information that the users provide to us related to the services for which they engage us.
    * Directly and indirectly from activity on our website (www.Kongregate.com). For example, from submissions through our website portal or website usage details collected automatically.
    * From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the services we perform. For example, from vendors who provide services to us.
3. **Use of Personal Information.**
    
    We may disclose your Personal Information to a third party for a business purpose. “Personal information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular you as consumer or a household. When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.
    
    |     |     |     |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | **Categories of Personal Information** | **Disclosed to Which Categories of Third Parties for Operational Business Purposes** | **Retention Period** |
    | Personal information as defined in the California customer records law, such as name, contact information and government-issued ID | Affiliates, service providers, business partners in case of contest, sweepstakes, and promotion, legal authorities | Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years. |
    | Commercial Information, such as transaction information and purchase history | Affiliates, service providers, business partners in case of contest, sweepstakes, and promotion, legal authorities | Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years. |
    | Internet or network activity information, such as interactions with our online properties | Affiliates, service providers, business partners in case of contest, sweepstakes, and promotion, legal authorities | Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years. |
    | Identifiers, such as username, contact information, IP address and other online identifiers | Affiliates, service providers, business partners in case of contest, sweepstakes, and promotion, legal authorities | Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years. |
    | Geolocation Data, such as approximate location derived from IP address | Affiliates, service providers, business partners in case of contest, sweepstakes, and promotion, legal authorities | Annual deletion of user accounts that have not engaged in any form of login activity over the course of at least three consecutive years. |

    We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:
    
    * To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided.
    * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
    * To provide you with email alerts, event registrations and other notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you.
    * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collections.
    * To improve our website and present its contents to you.
    * For testing, research, analysis and product development.
    * As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our clients or others.
    * To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
    * As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
    * To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred.
    * We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.
    
    _We do not “sell” and have not “sold” Personal Information for purposes of the CCPA in the last 12 months._
    
    We do not process Sensitive Personal Information of yours. Sensitive personal information includes personal data that discloses:
    
    * Government-issued identification numbers like social security, driver's license, state identification card, or passport numbers.
    * Financial information such as account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card numbers when combined with security codes, passwords, or access credentials to access an account.
    * Precise geolocation data.
    * Details about racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, or membership in a union.
    * The contents of your mail, email, and text messages, but only if the entity receiving the information is not the intended recipient.
    * Genetic data.
4. **Your Rights**
    
    If you are a resident of California, you have the following rights:
    
    * Right to Delete Personal Information: You have the right to request that we delete your Personal Information. Depending on the specific case, exceptions can apply to this right, e.g., if we have to keep your information to comply with legal obligations or to ensure the freedom of expression (Section 1798.105 CCPA).
    * Right to Correct Inaccurate Personal Information: You have the right to request the correction of Personal Information we maintain about you (Section 1798.106 CCPA).
    * Right to Know What Personal Information is Being Collected: You have the right to request the following information from us (Section 1798.110 and 1798.115 CCPA):
        * The categories of personal information we have collected about you.
        * The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected.
        * The business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information.
        * The categories of third parties to whom we disclose personal information.
        * The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
        * The categories of personal information that we sold or shared about you and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or shared, by category or categories of personal information for each category of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or shared.
        * The categories of personal information that we disclosed about you for a business purpose and the categories of persons to whom it was disclosed for a business purpose.
    * Right to Opt-Out of Sale and Sharing: We do not sell your Personal Information. We share your Personal Information with advertising partners to show you ads that might be more interesting to you. You have the right to opt out of any sale or sharing of your Personal Information (Section 1798.120 CCPA). Please see Section (Opting Out of Promotional Emails from Kongregate) of this Privacy Policy on how to do this.
    * Right to Limit the Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information: Even though we do not process Sensitive Personal Information of yours, we’d like to also inform you that you principally have the right to limit the use or disclosure of your Sensitive Personal Information should we be using such data of yours beyond what is reasonable and proportionate to provide the requested services or other purposes permitted by the CCPA (Section 1798.121 CCPA).
    * Right of No Retaliation Following Opt Out or Exercise of Other Rights: If you exercise your CCPA rights, you have the right that we do not unlawfully treat you in a detrimental way (Section 1798.152 CCPA). Please note though, that depending on your request, features within our game might not work the same way as they would have without **your request (e.g., if you want to see ads that might interest you more).**
5. **Data Subject Rights (GDPR)**
    
    If the GDPR applies when you use our Services, you have certain rights which you can find listed below. If the GDPR does not apply when you use our Services (e.g., you reside in the USA), these rights do not necessarily apply.
    
    * **Right of information:** You have the right to be provided information regarding the processing of your personal data by us, in accordance with Art. 13 and 14 GDPR.
    * **Right of access:** You have the right to obtain confirmation as to whether we are processing your personal data and, if this should be the case, access to the personal data, in accordance with Art. 15 GDPR.
    * **Right to rectification:** You have the right to obtain rectification of inaccurate or incomplete personal data concerning you, in accordance with Art. 16 GDPR.
    * **Right to erasure (“right to be forgotten”):** Under certain circumstances you have the right to obtain the erasure of personal data concerning you, in accordance with Art. 17 GDPR.
    * **Right to restriction:** Under certain circumstances you have the right to obtain the restriction of processing, in accordance with Art. 18 GDPR.
    * **Right to data portability:** Under certain circumstances you have the right to receive the personal data concerning you, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and the right to transmit this data to another controller, in accordance with Art. 20 GDPR.
    * **Right to object:** Under certain circumstances you have the right to object to the processing of personal data concerning you, in accordance with Art. 21 GDPR. This includes but is not limited to the right to object in cases in which we process your personal data on the legal basis of Art. 6 para. 1 let. f) GDPR.
    * **Right to lodge a complaint:** You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of the EU of your habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if you consider that the processing of personal data relating to you infringes the GDPR, as set out in Art. 77 GDPR.
    * **Right to withdraw consent:** If a processing of your personal data is based on your consent as set out in Art. 6 para. 1 let. a) GDPR or Art. 9 para. 2 let. a) GDPR, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, in accordance with Art. 7 para. 3 GDPR. Such withdrawal does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
    * **Right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing:** You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you, as set out in Art. 22 para 1 GDPR.
    
    **To make a request for the disclosures or deletion described above, please contact us at privacy@kongregate.com or [use this form](javascript:util.openURL('https://kongregate-privacy.my.onetrust.com/webform/7424cb27-7013-49a6-a5a7-66b4bfa6c20e/167536ab-aa15-479c-8e0f-0b2911ce1d1e')). You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period.**
    
6. **CCPA Metrics Report.**
    
    |     |     |     |     |
    | --- | --- | --- | --- |
    | **Request type** | **Quantity** | **Stage** | **Status** |
    | Deletion Request | 1682 | Complete | Completed request |
    | Deletion Request | 5363 | Incomplete | Incomplete due to: Incomplete/partial data, Request for more information, Failed to verify identity |
    | Access Request | 130 | Complete | Completed request |
    | Access Request | 619 | Incomplete | Incomplete due to: Incomplete/partial data, Request for more information, Failed to verify identity |

Email Address

 Send me updates

Password _(min. 10 characters)_

Date of Birth

January Febuary March April May June July August September October November December 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 1940 1941 1942 1943 1944 1945 1946 1947 1948 1949 1950 1951 1952 1953 1954 1955 1956 1957 1958 1959 1960 1961 1962 1963 1964 1965 1966 1967 1968 1969 1970 1971 1972 1973 1974 1975 1976 1977 1978 1979 1980 1981 1982 1983 1984 1985 1986 1987 1988 1989 1990 1991 1992 1993 1994 1995 1996 1997 1998 1999 2000 2001 2002 2003 2004 2005 2006 2007 2008 2009 2010 2011 2012 2013 2014 2015 2016 2017 2018 2019 2020 2021

Username _(4-16 characters)_

 I have read and agree to the [Privacy Policy](https://www.kongregate.com/privacy), [User Agreement](https://www.kongregate.com/user-agreement) and [Cookie Policy](https://www.kongregate.com/cookie-policy)

Parent or guardian email address _Your parent or guardian must review and agree on your behalf to register_

​

Join the conversation Join Discord

© 2024 Kongregate

Loading ​
